excuse me sir question for you how old
were you when you became a millionaire
you have to ask a millionaire what do
you mean I'm a billionaire you're a
billionaire yeah how old were you when
you became a billionaire oh in my 50s
and what lot of business were you in the
hospitality business what were you doing
in Hospitality I own hotels all over the
world 35 countries Hilton owns my
company today Hilton bought your company
Hilton bought my company and I go all
over the world interviewing the most
successful business owners could I get
one quick minute with you real quick for
the channel sure do you come from a lot
of money no I started with negative $20
million unfortunately my father went
broke I had to pay it off so I didn't
start from zero I started $20 million
try that party trick but you've sold
billions of dollars throughout your
career what is a billionaire secret to
sales listen is that simple listen the
customer your friends your Bankers will
always tell you the pathway listen but
what's your best negotiation advice as a
billionaire put the pen across the table
and the first person who talks loses
break that down when the deal is ripe it
solves itself put the pen across the
table and shut up what's the lesson of
about money that Banks don't want people
to know I never negotiated with my Banks
don't negotiate with your Banks make
sure you make your Banks a ton of money
they'll always be there for you what do
you mean by that cuz Banks running the
business and making money for themselves
we all made a lot of money together
everyone was always paid back and what's
more important in business what you know
or who you know it's both relationships
are always very important but a matter
of fact you got to stay out of one ZIP
code the zip code of bad people if
they're around your life make them go
away don't go in that zip code thank you
so much for your time I appreciate you
you're welcome man